How many options do we have?
We have 60 lakhs of properties.
We are at the top of the channel.
Okay.
We have come down from here.
We have to change a button to compare banks.
Okay, next.
We have come down from here.
Let me tell you something.
Right now, we have banks.
Lenders.
If we talk about lenders, we don't even have banks.
But we have lenders everywhere.
Banks are in everyone's mind.
So, when we go forward,
we have lenders.
Earlier, we used to say, get a fair view of home loans
and apply to your chosen banks.
But we have lenders everywhere.
We have lenders everywhere.
NBFC.
NBFC is a housing company.
We don't have a bank.
We do have a bank.
Some people think
that banks don't have NBFC
but everybody knows about NBFC.
It's a bank.
They know that
there exists something known as NBFC.
He will have a doubt that only banks have NBFCs.
But who does not know that there is something known as NBFC?
He thinks everything is bank.
But the one who is knowledgeable, who wants to impress the first person,
he knows that.
Yes, he knows about lenders and banks.
He knows everything about banks.
Where should we use neutral?
All...
Neutral means lenders, right?
Yes.
Bank specific bank.
All loan options.
You can go to your uncle and tell him.
Yes, yes.
Why not?
I don't know.
There is a requirement of 2 lakhs.
You have an income of 1 lakh.
You can leave all this.
Uncle's wish.
Suppose we gave him credit cards.
He doesn't know.
He uses a lender.
It's okay.
It's just a term.
Yes, it's okay.
For now...
We don't know what to do.
We are going to put a plug-in.
You capture all the customer interaction in the form of video.
And then we understand how people are.
Then we have to do these small things.
And then we have to help him.
Now...
What you have done...
The header block.
It looks good.
It means...
You have written all this.
Lender...
I don't know if it's high or low.
Now...
The color is also different.
We don't know the header.
Now...
This is just a table.
There is a little gap.
There is a little gap between the buttons and the table.
There is a little gap between the headers.
A little more.
Or you can put it like this.
This is a table.
Yes, you have to do that.
But it's too much.
Okay, this is a table.
Oh...
Then...
How should I show this?
This...
Chrome circle.
Yes, the tab switcher.
Actually, it should only be in these four columns.
No.
The name of the bank is the same.
The tab switcher.
So...
What does this overview do?
What is the shape of this overview?
Basically, it should be drawn like this.
Means...
Now this...
Means it should be drawn like this.
The way it looks from the top.
Yes, this is the same for Chrome.
But...
Why does this tab only apply to columns?
Then...
It should be like this.
I clicked here.
It should be seen only here.
But doesn't the design look weird?
Or is it written in the middle only?
No, I don't think it's a problem.
Because...
It will be here only.
I need to teach someone to apply.
Because a lot of things will come here today.
Okay.
There will be a feedback review.
Not now.
Keep it here.
It will be here only.
And in fact...
In fact...
It will be here only.
Done. It's perfect.
And...
Here...
Where the edit is...
The tabs will be there.
From the edit...
What does the edit do?
It will edit.
No edit.
Then let it scroll by itself.
Basically...
Yes, let it go.
If you go to Mintra or something...
The cards are not same to same.
The selections are...
In a strict manner.
You can change it here.
Keep it like that.
If you want to go up, you can edit it.
No, no. Do it.
Form goes up, answer goes down.
How did it go up?
I need a button.
Okay.
And the view should be like...
Exactly like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Basically, these four columns...
Belong to this tab.
If I switch tabs, there are different columns.
If I switch tabs again, there are different columns.
If you make a very clear mental picture...
That...
These five tabs...
Are important for me.
For everything.
In every tab, these columns are important.
This means...
You get to learn all the home runs here.
Games.
Just...
Write, UX.
You don't get to read the guide.
I mean...
If you have a home run, you have to judge it from five parameters.
Defaults.
Rate, loan, tenure, EMI.
Processing charges.
Legal charges.
Legal formats.
These are the five aspects.
Then...
There are four types of charges in processing charges.
This comes from here.
The models are...
Interact, code, code.
And...
The UI fits.
It fits perfectly.
I remember this.
I remember...
When I was making a sandwich...
There was a sandwich.
I put it here.
I cut it.
I didn't have to do anything.
I was learning.
I put it here.
I didn't say this.
People don't know about problems.
They think it's a problem.
Perfect.
Cooking doesn't have to be like this.
For six or nine months.
That's what it is.
I have mastered this process.